[
  {
    "question": "لوفي",
    "response": "لوفي"
  },
  {
    "question": "زورو",
    "response": "زورو"
  },
  {
    "question": "سانجي",
    "response": "سانجي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ناروتو",
    "response": "ناروتو"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساسكي",
    "response": "ساسكي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساكورا",
    "response": "ساكورا"
  },
  {
    "question": "كاكاشي",
    "response": "كاكاشي"
  },
  {
    "question": "إيتاشي",
    "response": "إيتاشي"
  },
  {
    "question": "غوكو",
    "response": "غوكو"
  },
  {
    "question": "فيجيتا",
    "response": "فيجيتا"
  },
  {
    "question": "غوهان",
    "response": "غوهان"
  },
  {
    "question": "إيرين",
    "response": "إيرين"
  },
  {
    "question": "ليفاي",
    "response": "ليفاي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ميكاسا",
    "response": "ميكاسا"
  },
  {
    "question": "آرمن",
    "response": "آرمن"
  },
  {
    "question": "غون",
    "response": "غون"
  },
  {
    "question": "كيلوا",
    "response": "كيلوا"
  },
  {
    "question": "كورابيكا",
    "response": "كورابيكا"
  },
  {
    "question": "هيسوكا",
    "response": "هيسوكا"
  },
  {
    "question": "لايت",
    "response": "لايت"
  },
  {
    "question": "إل",
    "response": "إل"
  },
  {
    "question": "ريوك",
    "response": "ريوك"
  },
  {
    "question": "ميليوداس",
    "response": "ميليوداس"
  },
  {
    "question": "بان",
    "response": "بان"
  },
  {
    "question": "ديان",
    "response": "ديان"
  },
  {
    "question": "إليزابيث",
    "response": "إليزابيث"
  },
  {
    "question": "كانكي",
    "response": "كانكي"
  },
  {
    "question": "توكا",
    "response": "توكا"
  },
  {
    "question": "رينجي",
    "response": "رينجي"
  },
  {
    "question": "إيتشيغو",
    "response": "إيتشيغو"
  },
  {
    "question": "أوراهارا",
    "response": "أوراهارا"
  },
  {
    "question": "ناتسو",
    "response": "ناتسو"
  },
  {
    "question": "غراي",
    "response": "غراي"
  },
  {
    "question": "لوسي",
    "response": "لوسي"
  },
  {
    "question": "إيرزا",
    "response": "إيرزا"
  },
  {
    "question": "سيباستيان",
    "response": "سيباستيان"
  },
  {
    "question": "سيل",
    "response": "سيل"
  },
  {
    "question": "ريفي",
    "response": "ريفي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ماكا",
    "response": "ماكا"
  },
  {
    "question": "سول",
    "response": "سول"
  },
  {
    "question": "يوجي",
    "response": "يوجي"
  },
  {
    "question": "غوجو",
    "response": "غوجو"
  },
  {
    "question": "ماكي",
    "response": "ماكي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ميغومي",
    "response": "ميغومي"
  },
  {
    "question": "شينرا",
    "response": "شينرا"
  },
  {
    "question": "آرثر",
    "response": "آرثر"
  },
  {
    "question": "رين",
    "response": "رين"
  },
  {
    "question": "يوكي",
    "response": "يوكي"
  }
]